{"data":[{"question":"___ should be planted in the shade.","a":"This kind of flowers","b":"These kind of flowers","c":"These kinds of flowers","d":"This kind flower","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- This kind of + flower (not \"flowers\")\n\n- These + plural noun-> These kinds (not \"these kind\")","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like to make ___ with you.","a":"friend","b":"a friend","c":"the friend","d":"friends","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: Make friends with somebody: to become friendly with people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"That fact is of great scientific ___.","a":"interest","b":"interesting","c":"interested","d":"interests","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Of + noun\/noun phrase\n\n- Noun phrase: Adj\/noun+ noun-> great scientific interest\n\n- That fact is (metion \"singular subject)-> interest (singular object)\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher gave me ___.","a":"many good advice","b":"many good pieces of advice","c":"many good advices","d":"many pieces of good advice.","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Advice: uncoutable noun\n\n- Structure: Piece of somthing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She was almost killed. The car missed her by a hair's ___.","a":"breadth","b":"length","c":"width","d":"thickness","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Hair's breadth: A small space, distance, or margin","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You should always keep a close ___ on the small children playing outdoors.","a":"care","b":"warning","c":"heed","d":"eye","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Keep a close eye: pay attention to","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"His visit saved me _________ of writing to him.","a":"the habit","b":"the occasion","c":"the opportunity","d":"the trouble","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Save somebody the trouble (of doing something): Save money\/ time\/ enery to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He must be near-sighted, for he wears ___.","a":"spectacle","b":"spectacles","c":"a spectacle","d":"a pair of spectacle","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Spectacles [plural]: glasses that help you see","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He was in _________ when he got married.","a":"thirties","b":"the thirties","c":"thirty age","d":"his thirties","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Thirties: The decade from 30 to 39 in a century","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ birthdays both come in October.","a":"My brother and sister's","b":"My brother and my sister","c":"My brother's and sister's","d":"My brother's sister's","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n-My brother's and sister's birthday= My brother's birthday and my sister's birthday","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}